giggag.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy

  * ### Introduction

GIGGAG, Inc. ("GIGGAG") takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously.

This privacy policy, which we adapted from a policy originally provided by [Automattic](http://www.automattic.com/) ([WordPress.com](http://www.wordpress.com/)), describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use our websites. Please read this notice very carefully.

  * ### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, GIGGAG collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GIGGAG's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GIGGAG's visitors use its website. From time to time, GIGGAG may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g. by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

GIGGAG also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. GIGGAG does not use such information to identify its visitors, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

  * ### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to GIGGAG's websites choose to interact with GIGGAG in ways that require GIGGAG to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GIGGAG gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for giggag.com to provide a username and email address. In each case, GIGGAG collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with GIGGAG. GIGGAG does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

  * ### Aggregated Statistics

GIGGAG may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, GIGGAG may monitor the most popular collections on giggag.com. GIGGAG may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GIGGAG does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

  * ### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

GIGGAG discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GIGGAG's behalf or to provide services available at GIGGAG's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using GIGGAG's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if GIGGAG or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that GIGGAG goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of GIGGAG may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, GIGGAG will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GIGGAG discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when GIGGAG believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GIGGAG, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a GIGGAG website and have supplied your email address, GIGGAG may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with GIGGAG and its products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GIGGAG takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

You should also be aware that if you submit information to "chat rooms," "forums" or "message boards" such information becomes public information, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications.

  * ### Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

We use cookies to understand and save user's preferences for future visits. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. 

If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly. 

  * ### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track and analyze our web traffic. **We do not have access to the information collected by Google** apart from what is displayed in our Google Analytics portal. 

We have implemented the following data collection features in Google Analytics: 

_1\. Remarketing with Google AdSense_

**Enables data collection for Display and Search Remarketing. This includes data from Google's signed-in users who have chosen to enable Google to associate their web and app browsing history with their Google account, and to use such information from their Google account to personalize ads. Google Analytics temporarily joins these identifiers to your Google Analytics data in order to support your audiences. When you enable this setting, you must adhere to the Google Analytics Advertising Features Policy, including rules around sensitive categories and the necessary privacy disclosures to your end users about the data you collect and share with Google.**

_2\. Advertising Reporting Features_

**Enables Advertising Reporting features like Audience Demographics and Interests Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager reporting, DoubleClick Bid Manager reporting, and Google Display Network Impression Reporting that help you better understand your users.**

The information collected by Google may be linked to your Google account if you're signed in. Google may also collect information relating to your: 

    * browsing device;
    * location;
    * operating system.

Please read Google's Privacy Policy for more information on how your data is collected and used: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

To opt out of Google's data collection, you may also set your browser to block all cookies, including cookies associated with our services. 

### Google Adsense

We display advertisement powered by Google Adsense. Google Adsense uses the information Google collects to display the most useful ads online. When you're signed in to your Google Account, they will also collect information that they store with your Google account. We do not have access to any data collected by Google for the purposes of advertising. 

You may choose to opt out of personalised advertisements by disabling cookies. 

  * ### Other Ads

Ads appearing on any GIGGAG websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by GIGGAG and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

  * ### Links to Third Party Sites

This privacy policy only applies to information collected by GIGGAG. This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that GIGGAG does not own or control, or employees that GIGGAG does not manage. A GIGGAG website may contain links to third party websites. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and GIGGAG and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

  * ### Security

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers. 

  * ### Choice/Opt-out

If we ever send you information by email concerning new products, services or information that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request no further notices. 

  * ### Address Book Data

Any external address book data (email contacts, etc.) that a user voluntarily gives GIGGAG access to will only be used for the described feature (looking up friends, etc.), and will not be stored or repurposed.

  * ### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, GIGGAG may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in GIGGAG's sole discretion. GIGGAG encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

  * ### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our sites in general, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
